KEITH ROBINSON

Maple Grove, MN 55369 (702) 510-3268 krobnson@mail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Customer-oriented sales professional with software engineer experience in websites and designs, user experience, usability and speed for multiple types of end-users. Successful Project manager from design to costing to production. Experienced in providing the highest level of customer-service.

SKILLS

- Web Site Design Software coding (Javascript, React, Ruby on Rails)
- Project Management (estimating)
- Retail Sales and B2B sales
- Business Analysis
- Leadership and sales (Dale Carnegie)
- Coaching (teaching golf)
- Strong and engaging interpersonal communication skills

- Microsoft 365 (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
- CRM, Peoplesoft, Opera
- Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Premiere)
- Photography (Canon)
- Hardware and software installation
- Data management (Firebase, AWS, SQL)

WORK HISTORY

Software Engineer 03/2016 to 11/2019

SCC (Remote Contactor) – Maple Grove, Minnesota

- Created new business for software web solutions. From single page to Cloud services.
- Used programming capabilities in Javascript, React, Ruby on Rails and other libraries as needed.
- Developed, coded, and updated and company sites for clients in Financial Service industry.
- Created site layout and used interface using HTML and CSS (SASS) practices.
- Researched new technologies, software packages, frameworks, and mobile products.
- Collaborated with in-house web designers to create sleek and innovative UI design.
- Pitched in to assisted senior developers to meet pressing deadlines during under-staffed periods in transition from WordPress to React.

Golf Professional 04/2005 to 12/2017

Wynn Las Vegas – Las Vegas, Nevada

- Organized daily outings and tournaments for casino and corporate events at club, which led to year over year increase in rounds played.
- Developed on going relationships with guests, providing course management, lessons, general information and concierge services.
- Maintained equipment, facilities and inventory to the Wynn standards.
- Evaluated staff skills and strength and assigned team positions to maximize talent areas.
- Successfully lead team through peak periods when understaffed.

• Coached C-level guests on their golf games, products, and equipment, which provide information needed to make appropriate purchases.

Professional Golf Caddie 09/2002 to 03/2005

Cascata Golf Club (Caesars Entertainment) – Boulder City, Nevada

- Established and maintained productive working relationships with staff and guests.
- Assisted guests with course management and logistics.
- Was available as needed.

Project Manager 09/2001 to 09/2002

Top Tool Company – Minneapolis, MN

- Lead sales team that lead to several new business projects.
- Prepared and reviewed engineering drawing and documentation specifications, scope of work, cost estimating, and other documents.
- Oversaw design and constructed bill of materials, including scheduling flow charts.
- Evaluated change order requests in response to revision updated and cost impact studies.
- Analyzed blueprints and delivered concise instructions to technical teams to maintain quality control.

EDUCATION

Certification: Full Stack Software Developer

Bloc.io - San Francisco, CA

- Bootcamp coursework in HTML, CSS and Javascript
- JavaScript, Ruby on Rails and Angular projects

Business Administration

University of Minnesota – Twin Cities – Minneapolis, MN

INTERESTS

- Photography: Canon EOS 5D Mark IV, full line of L-lenses
- Golf: still play to a 0 index. Fly fishing: Health and Fitness enthusiast. Avid reader: Try for a book a week.
- Collect Guitars: Prize Les Paul '58